Do you ever have a task that needs doing, but however urgent it is, you just don't get down to it?
你是否曾经有一项需要完成的任务，但是不管它有多紧急，你就是不着手去做呢？
From doing the housework to writing an assignment, there's always something I can put off until tomorrow.
从做家务到写作业，总是有些事情我可以推迟到明天再做。
Being a procrastinator is quite easy.
成为一个拖延者很容易。
There are so many other more interesting distractions such as watching funny cat videos on the internet or catching up with friends on social media!
还有很多其他更有趣的让人分心的事物，比如在互联网上看看有趣的猫咪视频，或者在社交媒体上和朋友们叙旧！
But Benjamin Franklin, one of the Founding Fathers of the United States, once wisely said that: 'You may delay, but time will not', in other words, the time we waste now is gone forever - so maybe I should pull my socks up and get on with what I should be doing.
但是美国开国元勋之一的本杰明·富兰克林曾经明智地说过：“你可以拖延，但时间不会”，换句话说，我们现在浪费的时间一去不复返了——所以也许我应该振作起来，继续去做我应该做的事情。
The reason why many of us delay doing something is that we live for the present not the future.
我们很多人拖延做某事的原因是我们为当下而活，而不是为未来而活。
We are reluctant to engage in tasks that relate to the future - sorting something out now that will benefit us in the future doesn't seem a priority.
我们不愿意去做那些与未来相关的任务——现在解决一些对未来有益的事情似乎不是优先考虑的事情。
Daphna Oyserman, Professor of Psychology at the University of Southern California, says: "Many of the future things that are very important require that we start now rather than later... Later means we don't have a lot of time left."
南加州大学的心理学教授达夫娜·奥伊瑟曼说：“许多与未来非常重要的事情都要求我们现在就开始行动，而不是等到以后......等到以后意味着我们没有太多时间了。”
So get cracking now rather than have a last-minute panic!
所以现在就去做吧，而不是到最后一刻才惊慌失措！
But it's hard to muster any enthusiasm when there are tedious chores to be done, so how can I control my lack of focus and knuckle down to what really needs to be done?
但是，当有乏味的琐事要做时，很难鼓起任何热情，那么我该如何控制自己注意力不集中，并开始认真做真正需要做的事情呢？
One idea is temptation bundling - doing two activities together - one that is boring but essential and one that you enjoy but isn't so productive.
一个想法是诱惑捆绑——将两项活动一起做——一项无聊但必不可少，另一项你喜欢但效率不高。
Planning is essential too and we should never underestimate how long things will take us.
计划也很重要，我们绝不应低估事情会花费我们多长时间。
However, Dr Catherine Loveday from Westminster University warns us about a 'planning fallacy' thinking we can get something done quickly.
然而，威斯敏斯特大学的凯瑟琳·洛夫迪博士警告我们注意“计划谬误”，即认为我们可以快速完成某事。
She says "We never seem to get any better at judging how long things will take us."
她说：“我们在判断事情需要多长时间方面似乎从未有所提高。”